So let me tell you one of the very big contrasts that has so many people wholly frustrated about Palestine in a way that I think people feel like they're not as frustrated about Congo.
We can see the conflict in the Congo and there is nobody refuting that conflict.
There is nobody saying there's no conflict in the Congo.
There is nobody saying that people aren't being killed in the Congo.
There is nobody saying that resources are not being stolen from the Congo.
There is no federal government every single day saying, no, we're not using your money to kill all the people in the Congo.
And even if they are doing that and not talking about it, they're not gaslighting the fucking world.
So if you're confused as to why people are so up in arms about Palestine, that should help you.
Literally, so much of this Palestinian problem is that these people don't want to fucking act like it's a problem.
That's what so many of us are like continuing to simply push across the finish line.
Just admission that a real thing is happening.
Yes.
So when people come to my fucking comments and say things like, I wish people had the same energy of this for Congo, you don't even have the same energy about this for the Congo.
Shut the fuck up.